Hey, Hayato.
喂，隼人
Some bitch threw up in the pool, it's crazy.
有個女的在泳池裡吐了，超扯的
Tanuki!
狸貓！
You should go, Tanuki!
你快走吧，狸貓！
I'm coming in.
我要進來囉
I'm dizzy.
好暈
Is this Hachi's room?
我們跑到小八的房間了？
But we were in Ippongi's room. What happened?
但我們剛才在一本木家裡 怎麼回事？
I brought you guys here.
是我帶你們過來的
Through the world of shadows.
穿越影子世界
What?
你幹嘛？
Is this real? It's not a metaverse?
這是真的嗎？不是虛擬世界嗎？
It's real! We can't log out!
是真的！我們無法登出！
I have to create an altar to adorn this head.
我必須建造一個祭壇擺上這顆頭
Where can I put this until then?
能先借放在哪裡嗎？
Of course not.
當然不行
Let's escape.
我們快逃吧
She's a demon. No, a murderer.
她是惡魔，不對，是殺人犯
I have extremely good hearing.
我的聽力非常敏銳
Maybe I shall cut your throat
為了不再讓你在背後說壞話
so you can never speak ill again.
乾脆割斷你的喉嚨
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字？
-Sorry. -A question for you, Sorry.
–抱歉 –抱歉，我想問你一件事
He's Tanuki, not Sorry.
他叫狸貓，不叫抱歉
Tanuki. Is there an underground ice cave nearby?
狸貓，附近有沒有地下冰穴？
I don't know.
我不知道
Hey, can't you put back that head in the shadows?
話說，妳不能把那顆頭 放回影子世界嗎？
No?
不行嗎？
I need this for an important ritual.
我有個重要的儀式需要用到這個
And you'll cooperate.
你們會幫忙吧？
Of course. Totally. Right?
當然，沒問題，對吧？
Hachi, sorry. I can't stand this.
小八，對不起，我受不了了
I'm logging out.
我要登出
Hey! Wait!
喂！等等！
HAVE YOUR DAD ARREST HER!
請你爸爸逮捕她！
You must never speak of this.
這件事你絕對不能說出去
Anyone who obstructs my mission, I will freeze the blood in their veins,
任何阻礙我完成的人 我會凍結他們體內的血液
extract their spine and intestines
挖出他們的脊椎和腸子
and devour their heart!
並且吞噬他們的心臟！
Understand?
明白嗎？
Yes.
是的
It's as if he was instantly frozen.
像是被瞬間冷凍一樣
The wound is clean.
切口很俐落
And no sign of the head anywhere.
而且到處都找不到頭顱
A headless corpse on a newly assigned site
我才剛派到這裡來，就出現無頭屍體
is quite punk! Is this common?
超龐克的！這種事很常見嗎？
No.
不常見
Sleep.
睡吧
A lot of young people are into mysticism and the occult these days.
現在很多年輕人 熱衷於神秘主義和超自然現象呢
I've seen this symbol on social media.
這個符號我在社群媒體上見過
It's a trend.
這是一種流行
The cause seems to run deeper than that.
但這起案件似乎有更深層的原因
The victim from the Ippongi Clan holds significant power.
受害者一本木家族掌握龐大的權力
Many enemies, too.
也樹敵不少
But first, gather evidence.
但首先，我們要收集證據
Sir, may I have a moment?
警部，方便說句話嗎？
Nothing.
這下沒輒了
We couldn't find the victim's head in the other room, either.
我們找不到受害者的頭顱 另一個房間裡也沒有
We'll ask the people in the vicinity.
去問問他身邊的人吧
The Yokai have come to our world.
那個妖怪來到了這邊的世界
In just one night, one of the Five Spears died.
僅僅一個晚上 就殲滅了五矛會的其中一個家族
Hey.
喂
This isn't a sumo ring salt toss.
又不是在相撲場上灑鹽
Gather fingerprints less dramatically.
採集指紋別搞得那麼誇張
Ten thousand apologies, Master.
萬分抱歉，主人
Of course, as you desire.
我絕不會再反抗您的旨意
What is his problem?
他有什麼毛病？
Forensics seem to have some peculiar characters.
鑑識科總是會有一些古怪的角色
You know, Izzy...
聽我說，伊姬…
I find you to be a very intriguing person.
我覺得妳非常有意思
And very cute, too.
而且也很可愛
Hold on.
等我一下
An icehouse?
那是冰窖嗎？
We call it a refrigerator.
現在叫做冰箱
So, Izzy.
就是說，伊姬
We've become partners,
我們雖然成為了伴侶
but it seems quite challenging.
但似乎困難重重
I mean... I'm sorry for performing the summoning ritual.
我的意思是… 我很抱歉進行了召喚儀式
But that was an accident.
但那是意外
So, I think it's better for us to part ways.
所以我認為，我們分開會比較好
You're a great person.
妳是很棒的人
It's not your fault. It's my fault.
這不是妳的錯，一切都要怪我
I've told you.
我說過了
We are connected through a bond that has been passed down since ancient times.
我和你締結了自古流傳下來的契約
There's no escaping it.
是沒辦法逃避的
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思？
Using your terms,
用你們的語言來說的話
we are in a boyfriend-girlfriend relationship.
我們之間算是男女朋友的關係
But there are times
就算是男女朋友的關係
when boyfriends and girlfriends part ways.
有時候也是會分開的
There is no parting for us. It's an eternal and sacred bond.
我們不會分開 我們的羈絆是永恆且神聖的
You're sweating.
你出汗了
Sorry, I'm nervous.
抱歉，我一緊張就會這樣
I need to bond more with you.
我需要和你締結更深厚的羈絆
You mean, again?
也就是說，要再來一次？
But we just talked about what to do with our relationship,
但我們剛剛才在討論 該如何定義兩人的關係
and I don't know what to do in these situations.
我不知道這種時候該怎麼辦
-What do couples usually do? -Shut up.
–一般的情侶會怎麼做？ –住口
Let's at least be quiet. My family might wake up.
至少安靜一點，我的家人可能會醒來
You slept well.
你睡得很熟
So...
所以…
Last night was real, right?
昨晚發生的事是真的吧？
Indeed.
沒錯
We were able to share our power sufficiently.
我們充分地共享了彼此的力量
It feels like a dream.
感覺就像做夢一樣
It's not a dream.
這不是夢
Everything is fine.
一切都很順利
Please let it be a dream.
拜託讓這一切都是夢
I'm hungry.
我餓了
Let's eat.
我們去吃飯吧
Hey, wait!
喂，等等！
You can't! My family's downstairs.
不行！我的家人在樓下
What should I do?
這下該怎麼辦？
All right.
好吧
Let's go.
我們走吧
No!
不要…
Tadashi, what's with all the fuss?
忠士，一大早的在吵什麼？
What?
什麼？
Do you always fly around with this roller-coaster-like vibe?
妳都像坐雲霄飛車那樣飛來飛去嗎？
It's just an ordinary shadow walking.
這只是在影子中通行，稀鬆平常
It's time. I've got to go.
時間到了，我得走了
I have school and stuff.
我得去學校，還有很多事要做
And my stomach hurts.
而且我的肚子很痛
It was nice meeting you.
很高興見到妳
It seems you don't quite understand our bond.
看來你還是不太明白我們之間的羈絆
I do.
我明白
But you see, I have a life
但是，我有自己的生活
that involves ordinary things, not murder.
普通的生活，與殺人無關
So, bye.
那麼，再見
If I die, you'll die, too.
要是我死了，你也會死掉
Come again?
妳說什麼？
-What is this sweet scent? -It's a crepe.
–這是什麼甜甜的香味？ –是可麗餅
Hey! Hey, wait.
喂…等等
Could you elaborate on this dying thing?
死掉是怎麼回事，妳能解釋一下嗎？
You summoned me, so it's your responsibility to provide for me.
你召喚了我，所以有責任供養我
I recommend our most popular crepe,
我推薦我們最受歡迎的可麗餅
the chocolate strawberry with super violent whipped creme.
擠上超爆量鮮奶油的巧克力草莓口味
I request that.
我向你請求一份
-One, please. -Thank you.
–請給我一份 –謝謝
So, what do you mean I die?
妳剛剛說我會死是什麼意思？
Our souls are bound by a connection.
我們的靈魂因為羈絆而相連
We share our power.
共享彼此的力量
If I die, you would soon follow.
要是我死了，你也會馬上跟著死掉
Or, if you die, I would die.
或是說，要是你死了，我也會死
That's more likely.
這更有可能
Thanks for waiting.
久等了
Here you go.
請用
Have a good day.
好的，謝謝惠顧
Delicious!
真美味！
Now, let's get back to our mission.
好了，繼續來完成我們的使命吧
We must gather more heads of the accursed.
我們必須收集更多可憎之人的頭顱
Heads...
頭顱…
I see it now.
原來如此
I finally know what's wrong.
我終於知道哪裡有問題了
-Gathering heads! -No.
–收集頭顱這件事！ –不
You're hesitant about our bond.
你對我們的關係猶豫不決
You said it yourself. We help each other.
我們應該互相幫助 這不是你自己說的嗎？
I never said I'd help with murder!
我沒說我會幫忙殺人！
Fine.
好吧
It's a detour, but it can't be helped.
雖然是繞道而行，但也沒辦法
We'll perform the traditional engagement ceremony tonight.
今晚我們將依照傳統舉行文定儀式
Then, we'll be connected both physically and spiritually,
這麼一來，不只肉體 我們的心靈也能建立連結
and you'll gain self-awareness.
你也會開始有所自覺了
Engagement? Marriage?
文定是指…結婚？
Tonight, at your residence.
今晚在你的宅邸舉行
-You can't! -Why not?
–不行！ –為什麼？
I mean, It's too sudden.
畢竟這實在太突然了
I remembered, I'll be out tonight.
對了，今晚我要出門
Fine.
好吧
Wherever you go,
不管你去哪裡
I'll simply follow your trail through the shadows.
我只要透過影子就能跟著你
I will now acquire
我現在要去準備
a dance and outfit suitable for the engagement ceremony.
適合文定儀式的舞蹈和服裝
Okay, I get it!
好啦，我明白了！
Just hold on.
等等
It'd be a problem if we can't get int touch, so...
這樣的話 如果我們聯絡不上彼此會很麻煩…
Here.
給妳
What's this?
這是什麼？
That's your name.
是你的名字
Press this and you'll be connected to me.
按下這個按鈕就能聯繫上我
Put it on your ear.
放到耳朵上
Do you hear my voice?
有聽到我的聲音嗎？
I can hear your voice from this board!
我可以從這片板子聽見你的聲音
With this, we can communicate no matter where we are.
有了這個，無論在哪裡都可以交談
Is this modern sorcery?
這是現代的妖術嗎？
Amazing.
太棒了
Well, I have to go to class now.
那麼，我現在得去上課了
I'm so busy!
我好忙！
I have to practice.
我必須練習
The tournament is coming up.
比賽就快到了
So busy.
超忙的
I need to get more kills.
我得提升擊殺數才行
Busy.
我很忙
Hey! I'm giving the sign for help!
喂！我都已經打出求救暗號了！
Did we have such a sign?
我們有這種暗號嗎？
Do you intend to abandon me?
你打算棄我於不顧嗎？
We swore a blood oath of brotherhood when we were eight.
我們八歲就用口水結拜成兄弟
Have you forgotten? You were the one who found that spell!
你忘記了嗎？ 發現那個咒語的人是你！
I just showed you Stories.
我只是給你看IG限動
I summoned a Yokai!
我召喚了妖怪！
Your best friend ended up bonding with a killer Yokai that gains power from sex!
透過性愛獲得力量的殺人妖怪 跟你最好的朋友締結了關係
Don't you care?
你都無所謂嗎？
-Your words are interesting. -Stop being silly!
–這些詞彙擺在一起很有意思 –別再裝傻了！
She said she wants to gather more heads.
她說她想收集更多人頭
Seriously?
不會吧？
Dead serious. We need to drive her away somehow.
事態嚴重，我們得想辦法把她趕走
Have you told your dad?
你告訴你爸了嗎？
That there's a severed head in my fridge?
說我的冰箱裡有顆人頭？
How could I?
我怎麼說得出口？
Hurry up and tell him! Right now!
現在趕快跟他商量吧！
I can't. We never talk about anything.
我辦不到，我們平常都不會閒聊了
Wait, you put that thing in your fridge?
等等，你把那東西放進冰箱了嗎？
-Anyway! -Seriously?
–總之… –真的假的？
We need to find a solution now,
我們現在需要找到解決方法
while she's off preparing for some absurd engagement ceremony!
趁她去準備荒謬的文定儀式的時候！
Engagement?
文定？
I told you it's an emergency.
所以我才說事態緊急
But I bought her a smartphone with location tracking.
不過，我買了一支 可以定位追蹤的手機給她
It's on a 60-month installment plan!
分期付款60個月！
You're her stalker now?
你這樣根本是在跟蹤她
I'm kidding. Quite a thoughtful move for you.
開玩笑的，對你而言 算是很深思熟慮了
I've been thinking about something, too.
不過，我也一直在思考一件事
Your relationship with her is a curse.
你和她的關係是一種詛咒
And if it's a curse, you might be able to break it.
如果是詛咒，或許有辦法解除
This is quite a day's work.
這可能要查上一整天
Could take longer.
說不定更久
The curse that summoned Izzy was written in ancient divine characters,
召喚伊姬的詛咒是用神代文字撰寫的
but I have no idea what language this is.
但我完全不懂這是什麼語言
Boys.
你們兩個
That's a precious book, so handle it with care.
那是珍貴的書籍，要小心翻閱
Sorry, we're in a bit of rush.
抱歉，我們有點著急
You're...
你是…
Professor Sawada's...
妳是澤田教授的…
Ms. Arisa.
有紗小姐
I'm Tanuki, from the workshop.
我是狸貓，實習時曾受妳關照
Hello.
你好
Sanskrit sacred magic?
《梵文神聖魔法》？
The existence of ancient guardian spirits?
《遠古守護神靈的存在》？
What are you looking for?
你們在查什麼呢？
-You can read them? -Of course.
–妳看得懂？ –當然
We're looking for a ritual to banish Yokai from the human world.
我們在找 能將妖怪趕出人類世界的儀式
-Yokai? -For school.
–妖怪？ –這是課堂的報告
Did the professor give such an assignment?
教授有要你們交這樣的報告嗎？
I'm looking for a way to sever the spiritual connection
其實我們在找的是 能夠切斷妖怪與人類宿主之間
between a Yokai and its human host...
精神上的聯繫的方法…
Tanuki's into occult stuff, and sometimes says weird things.
狸貓喜歡這種超自然的東西 有時會說些奇怪的話
So, you're looking for a banishment ritual?
也就是說 你們在尋找驅逐惡靈的儀式？
Here.
這裡
BANISHMENT RITUAL
驅逐惡靈的儀式
This is an ancient exorcism ritual from ancient times.
這是自古流傳下來 驅逐惡靈儀式的咒語
It can deal with various entities.
可以對付各種惡靈
You know a lot.
妳很了解呢
My family is into mythology,
我的家人熱衷神話
so I like sorcery and ghost stories.
耳濡目染，我也喜歡妖術和怪談
I hope it works out.
希望你們一切順利
And make sure to put it back after you're done.
之後記得把書放回原位
Yes.
好的
She's a mysterious person.
她真是個神秘的人
I'm surrounded by mysterious things.
我的身邊充滿了神秘的事物
Speaking of, where's Izzy?
話說，伊姬在哪裡？
KAMAKURA CITY SEARCH: IZZY
鎌倉市，搜尋：伊姬
-Kamakura?
–鎌倉？
So the dance has survived in this era.
原來這種舞蹈有留存到這個時代
I like how you look, too.
妳們的服裝我也很喜歡
If she's in Kamakura, we have time.
如果她在鎌倉，我們似乎還有時間
Have you forgotten?
你忘記了嗎？
Izzy can teleport through shadows.
伊姬可以穿越影子瞬間移動
Let's take a note of this spell.
先拍下這個咒語吧
-I hope it works. -Yeah.
–希望有用 –是啊
-You look good! -Great!
–看起來很棒！ –很好！
Nice.
不錯
Smile.
笑一個
Great move!
跳得很棒！
You're doing great!
很會跳！
That's awesome!
棒極了！
Hey.
喂
What's that strange dance?
那是什麼古怪的舞蹈？
This dance is buzzing right now.
這支舞現在到處在瘋傳
Buzzing?
瘋傳？
It means it's trending.
很流行的意思
Like an epidemic?
像流行病一樣？
That's hilarious.
真好笑
She said epidemic.
居然說流行病
Do you want to dance, too?
妳也想跳跳看嗎？
-Yeah. -She should.
–對啊 –該跳一下
-We'll take you. -Go on.
–反正剛好 –跳吧
She's still in Kamakura, near the sea.
她還在鎌倉，靠近海邊
-Let's get ready now. -Yeah.
–趁現在做好準備 –好的
The ritual requires a magically protected location.
舉行儀式需要一個受魔法保護的地方
A quiet place where no one will disturb us at night...
一個晚上很安靜 沒人會打擾我們的地方
What about the abandoned school in Kitayama?
北山的廢棄學校怎麼樣？
Yeah!
就是那裡！
I'll drop by for practice and join you later.
好，我去練習露個臉，晚點去找你
Benitaro would be mad if we skip it.
如果我們都沒去，紅太郎會生氣
Got it. See you tonight.
知道了，晚上見
Have you heard anything from Hayato?
隼人有跟你說什麼線索嗎？
Nothing.
天曉得
Any financial troubles?
他有財務困難嗎？
It seems he was quite well off.
他好像過得滿奢華的
No clue.
天曉得
Your cousin was murdered. Can't you cooperate?
堂哥被殺了，你就不能合作一下嗎？
He seemed to be interested in mysticism.
他似乎對神秘主義很感興趣
Do you know anything?
你知道什麼嗎？
Like occultism or magic?
例如超自然現象或魔法之類的？
I said I don't know.
就說我不知道了
That was the first time I'd seen Hayato since he left his family.
隼人離家後 我是睽違已久第一次見到他
He left his family?
離家？
He didn't want to inherit his dad's position.
他不想接替父親繼承家業
So, he had a bad relationship with his father?
也就是說，他和父親關係不好？
Did they have conflicts?
他們該不會起了衝突？
I'm not saying Uncle killed him.
我可沒說伯伯殺了他
To begin with, they hardly even talked.
他們父子之間本來就幾乎不講話
Uncle always exaggerated things, talking about how they were protecting the world.
伯伯總是很誇張 說他們在保護這個世界
He was hard on others and overconfident.
他對人格外嚴厲，而且充滿自信
It's no wonder his son didn't like him.
被兒子討厭也不奇怪
Enough?
問夠了吧？
Thank you for your cooperation.
謝謝你的配合
Let's also talk to the victim's father, Takeru Ippongi.
我們也和受害者的父親 一本木健談談吧
You seem to be fixated on mysticism.
妳似乎很執著於神秘主義
Well, it's not normal.
不論怎麼看，這起案件都很不尋常
The corpse, the cut on the neck,
那具屍體，脖子的切口
and that room. We should follow every lead.
還有那個房間 我們要追蹤所有的線索
Don't casually mention things like the world of mysticism
不要輕易把神秘主義或魔法的事
or magic.
掛在嘴上
Why?
為什麼？
It doesn't exist, that's why.
因為那種東西並不存在
Nice.
很好
-Good job. -All right!
–做得好 –太好了！
All right! Nice game.
很好！這場打得很棒
Not bad, Terauchi.
寺內，你表現得不錯
Thank you.
謝謝誇獎
We'll kill those who bail.
偷懶沒來的人應該被宰掉
Why is Hachi skipping practice?
話說，為什麼小八翹掉練習？
He's probably struggling from that incident.
那起案件可能對他打擊很大
Why is Hachi struggling?
為什麼小八會受到打擊？
He wasn't even friends with Hayato.
他和隼人又不是朋友
He has to pull himself together.
告訴他要振作
We're aiming to win the next tournament.
我們的目標不是贏得下次比賽嗎？
Okay, I'll tell him.
好的，我會告訴他
Jeez, I'm starving.
天啊，我餓了
Do you have any snacks?
你有零食嗎？
What's this?
這是什麼？
Hey!
喂！
That's nothing.
不要亂碰啦
I'll head home first, then.
那我先告辭，我要回家了
Bye-bye! Adieu!
拜拜！再見！
Something seems suspicious.
總覺得有點可疑
I'm home.
我回來了
Welcome home.
歡迎回來
Mom's at a class reunion. Your dinner is in the fridge.
媽媽去參加同學會了，晚餐在冰箱裡
Where are you going?
你要去哪裡？
Just to the gym.
去一趟健身房
The gym? At this hour?
健身房？這麼晚去？
Tanuki and I decided to work out together.
我和狸貓決定一起健身
I see.
這樣啊
Do you know a kid named Hayato Ippongi?
忠士，你認識一個叫做 一本木隼人的年輕人嗎？
What?
什麼？
I think he's from your university.
他好像跟你們讀同一所大學
Sorry, I don't really know.
抱歉，我不太清楚
Okay.
好吧
I gotta go.
我得走了
Tadashi.
忠士
Never mind.
算了，沒事
I got them!
我買來了！
Finally. Hurry up!
你終於來了，快點進行吧！
I used my points so I got the offerings cheaper.
我用了點數，買到比較便宜的供品
I got a roasted chicken since I couldn't find
找不到剛宰殺的雞，所以…
a freshly slaughtered one.
我買了烤雞
I told Izzy about this place. She'll be here soon.
我跟伊姬說了這裡的位置 她應該很快就會過來
We're a good team, as expected.
我們果然合作無間
Look at this.
你看這個
Place them where the gravitational force intensifies, like in the diagram.
如圖所示 把供品放在強化咒力的位置
Got it.
知道了
FOLLOWERS
粉絲
TADASHI INUKAI
犬飼忠士
Do you know a kid named Hayato Ippongi?
你認識一個叫做 一本木隼人的年輕人嗎？
Sorry, I don't really know.
抱歉，我不太清楚
Is this party also part of the exorcism ritual?
辦這場派對 也是驅逐惡靈儀式的一部分？
It's for distracting her.
這是為了分散她的注意力
"I'm jere"?
“我到惹”？
She's here.
她過來了
It's freezing.
好冷
All right. I'll attract her to the center of this magic circle.
聽好，我會引她來魔法陣的中心
When I give the sign, read this spell.
你等我發出信號，就讀出這個咒語
Okay.
知道了
-Quick, hide! -All right.
–快躲起來！ –好
Hurry!
動作快！
Let's begin the engagement ceremony.
開始進行文定儀式吧
Through this, we will have a spiritual connection.
藉此，我們將建立心靈上的連結
This? I also prepared a party for the engagement.
這個嗎？我也準備了文定派對
A party is basically a way to celebrate.
派對就是一種慶祝的方式
Thank you.
謝謝
I offer this dance to you.
我要向你獻上這支舞蹈
To show my gratitude, I incorporated
為了表達謝意
the modern style into the traditional dance.
我在傳統舞蹈中融入了現代風格
With this, our bond is formally connected,
這麼一來 我們正式建立了相連的羈絆
mind and body.
不論心靈或是身體
You don't like it?
你不喜歡嗎？
No, not at all.
沒這回事
It was really great.
真的很精彩
It's my turn next.
接下來換我表現了
Have a seat.
坐吧
Why do I smell incense?
為什麼我聞到了線香的味道？
It's to cover up the musty odor.
是為了掩蓋霉味
This place isn't cleaned regularly.
這個地方沒有定期清掃
How about some wine?
要不要來點紅酒？
I don't drink.
我不喝酒
You're sweating.
你出汗了
What are you nervous about, Hachi?
你在緊張什麼，小八？
Izzy.
伊姬
Sorry.
對不起
Tanuki!
狸貓！
Return to the ancient world!
回到遠古的世界去吧！
Is it because I didn't use a freshly slaughtered chicken?
果然沒用剛宰殺的雞就不行嗎？
Tanuki!
狸貓！
It hurts.
好痛
You watch out! I have a weapon!
妳給我小心！我手上有武器！
I have shadows.
我有影子
I didn't mean to do that.
我不是有意的
What's this?
這是什麼？
Let me out!
放我出去！
Please! Let him out!
拜託，把狸貓放出來吧！
He ends here. I'll crush him to pieces.
他要死在這裡，我要讓他粉身碎骨
Wait, Izzy!
等等，伊姬！
We never intended to harm you.
我們並沒有打算要傷害妳
We were going to use the exorcism spell to send you to where you came from.
只是想用驅逐惡靈的咒語 把妳送回原本的地方
To the World of Nothing?
回到無間地獄？
We are bound by an eternal bond.
我們已經被永恆的羈絆緊緊相連了
Why can't you understand?
你為什麼不能理解？
It seems sacrificing your friend is the best way
為了讓你明白 我們之間的誓言有多重要
to make you understand the importance of our vow.
犧牲你的朋友似乎是最有效的方法了
Okay!
我明白了！
I accept everything about us, the bond, and all the magic!
不論是締結羈絆或是妖力 我願意接受妳的一切！
I'll stop all of this. No more exorcism spells.
我不會再這樣了 不會再使用驅逐惡靈的咒語
So, please.
所以，拜託妳
I promise you. Please spare Tanuki.
我答應妳，拜託放過狸貓吧
Don't kill my friend! Please.
不要殺害我的朋友，拜託
You betraying me is unforgivable.
你騙了我，不可原諒
And you didn't even like my dance.
而且你根本不喜歡我的舞蹈
I liked it.
我喜歡
Your dance was... You know, it was cute.
妳的舞蹈…怎麼說呢，很可愛
You're lying!
撒謊！
You're just trying to appease me!
你只是想討好我罷了！
Until you realize your mistake, I won't speak to you.
在你體認到自己犯的錯誤之前 我不會和你說話
She's crazy.
她太瘋狂了
I...
我…
I think my girlfriend's mad at me.
我好像惹女朋友生氣了
There you are.
妳在那裡啊
-That was delicious! -Yeah.
–剛才那個真好吃 –對啊
I want to drink a bit more.
我想再喝一點
Sounds good!
好喔